(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
Where are we going?
What if we're going abroad?
This is totally insane.
(What will be the mission location for Round 4?)
I didn't know we could get out from here.
Where are we going?
Where will we compete? It made me imagine all kinds of possibilities.
We're at Incheon Airport at night.
We're going up.
I felt stunned, like I got hit on the head.
(Where are they headed?)
Over here?
This is incredible.
What could the next mission be?
I will now announce the mission for Round Four.
Already?
- Here comes the mission.
- All of a sudden?
The Round Four mission is called...
Morning at the Airport.
Are we making breakfast?
- What a surprise.
- "Morning at the Airport?"
- Morning?
- Morning at the airport is...
the busiest time of day...
with the most flights and the highest number of passengers.
(The final gateway to the final round)
(Morning at the Airport)
(The start of a journey to destinations around the world)
(Of different nationalities)
(With different purposes)
(Countless people)
(A special moment before departure)
(Where travelers can enjoy performances on their way out)
(Incheon International Airport's departure area)
(The departure terminal is today's business district.)
(The airport food court that connects tourists with K-food)
Each team will open a station in the food court...
and serve breakfast...
from 6am to 9am.
- I didn't imagine this.
- In the morning?
I was wondering what approach we should take.
Will there be more foreign or Korean customers?
(Who will be the main customers? Koreans or foreigners?)
Something you can eat easily in the morning.
The key is food that people can eat quickly before leaving.
It's a place where people can get this and that.
They can share different dishes.
Since they're about to leave Korea,
it must be something distinctively Korean.
(Is Korean food advantageous in this district?)
This round will be conducted as a blind competition.
(Round 4 will be a blind competition.)
That's a relief. It works in our favor.
For this mission,
you can add one more part-time employee to your team.
We can add an employee.
The ingredient budget is up to each team.
The cost will be deducted from the final sales.
The menu and pricing are entirely up to the team.
- Net profit?
We're competing based on net profit?
In this mission,
only the top three teams...
with the highest sales will survive.
This will be hard.
Three teams?
Let's survive this round as well.
- Whatever it takes, let's make it.
- Let's make it.
We just have to win. I'm confident.
In this mission, there will be a special rule.
Another rule?
There will be...
a bidding war.
(Bidding war)
- What?
- "Bidding?"
Is it because of the shop location?
- It's a battle of locations.
- Bidding for shop locations?
Does each location cost a different amount?
What does it mean?
It must be him.
Hello, I'm auctioneer Kwak Jong Woo. I'll be overseeing the bidding war.
It's an auction.
Right in front of you,
there is a total of seven shop properties up for auction.
(Street Restaurant Fighter)
The lights turned on.
(7 food courts)
(A. Korean food station 1)
(B. Korean food station 2)
(C. Thai food station)
(D. Hot dog station)
(E. Pork cutlet station)
(F. Chinese food station)
(When you walk deeper inside)
If you win a shop through the auction,
including the kitchen equipment, appliances, and tableware,
you will have to use everything exactly as is.
(The existing kitchen and equipment must be used.)
Also, there's a total of five sales hooks...
to help promote your shop.
(Sales hook 2: A set of 3 medium LED posters)
(Sales hook 3: A set of 3 banners)
(Sales hooks 4, 5: Upper and lower display cases)
Everything you receive...
has to be obtained through the auction.
(Shops and sales hooks can only be acquired through bidding.)
Any money spent during the auction...
will be deducted from your sales.
(The more you spend, the bigger the loss.)
Since these are actual restaurants,
all the interiors are different.
We have to use the equipment that's already inside.
Looking at the kitchens,
- not a single one is the same.
- I know.
We're probably in for a chaotic battle.
(The bidding war starts.)
We're about to start...
- the shop auction.
- The shop?
The opening bid is ten dollars.
Every time someone raises their paddle,
the bid goes up by ten dollars.
I'm curious.
I feel like everyone is thinking the same thing.
First, Station A is a Korean food station.
(Station A used to sell bibimbap and soup with rice.)
It has two regular burners,
two low burners,
and one rotating stir-fry wok.
(A classic kitchen for Korean cuisine)
You can even make fried rice in here, right?
- Four burners?
- We can make other things too.
- Spicy stir-fried pork?
- This is the best.
We wanted Station A.
We can make bibimbap.
- Right.
- We can make so many things.
I really liked the kitchen.
If I were a customer,
I'd only get either A or B.
(Korean food A, Korean food B)
asked the staff who work here.
It has to be Korean food.
They said that there are a lot of foreigners here.
- We should sell Korean food.
- Right.
What sells the best here?
I'd say Korean food.
Korean food?
For breakfast, we must sell Korean food.
Yes, but...
(Most of them prefer the Korean food stations.)
Jong In, let's join them.
I want to hear what everyone else is saying.
(Quietly)
(Peeking)
Naengmyeon?
What is it? Please tell us.
Both Sung Hoon's team and Sang Hyun's team want...
the same thing as us.
- A is the best location.
- Yes.
The competition will be brutal.
- Seriously.
- How much will we have to spend?
(Many teams are hoping to win Korean food station A.)
It will be a game of reading the room.
I'm definitely taking this one.
The bidding starts at ten dollars.
Every bid goes up by ten dollars.
- We're winning this one.
- The auction will begin.
Ten dollars.
It's a ten-dollar bid.
(Kim Hoon, 10 dollars)
Twenty dollars.
We have a 30-dollar bid.
Forty dollars? I'll ask again.
Choi Sang Hyun was a little faster.
Fifty dollars is still available.
We have a 50-dollar bid.
Sixty dollars is available.
- Sixty dollars.
- Shall we go for it?
- Anyone for 60 dollars?
- Come on, 60 dollars is nothing.
Jung Ho Young, 60 dollars.
- Don't try to stir things up.
- How about 70 dollars?
Seventy dollars. Eighty dollars.
Ninety dollars.
Ninety dollars. How about a hundred?
- Take your time.
- I'll ask again.
Anyone for 110 dollars?
- Anyone for 120 dollars?
- Hoon is flexing.
- I'm going all in.
- One hundred and twenty dollars.
One hundred and thirty dollars.
Don't let them see you wavering.
Our strategy was to intimidate them...
so that they drop out.
Let's think about it when we get to Station B.
One hundred and thirty dollars.
For 130 dollars, Jung Ho Young was a bit faster.
One hundred and forty dollars.
I bet they'll go all the way.
One hundred and fifty dollars. One hundred and sixty dollars?
Jung Ho Young, I'll take your 170-dollar bid.
- Gosh.
- One hundred and eighty dollars.
- They'll go all the way.
- How about 190 dollars?
(Jung Ho Young, 190 dollars)
We have a 200-dollar bid.
- Anyone for 210 dollars?
- Look at Hoon.
Two hundred dollars? Goodness.
They might be deliberately driving up the price.
He's definitely going to do it. Let's drive up the price...
to make him spend more money.
Keep going. We'll go up to this price.
We have a bid. Two hundred and twenty dollars is available.
(The auction price is treated as rent and deducted from the sales.)
- Trust me.
- Anyone for 220 dollars?
Two hundred and twenty dollars.
- How about 230 dollars?
- Goodness.
- It's too expensive.
- How about 230 dollars?
- I'll buy even if it's 500 dollars.
- Anyone for 230 dollars?
- It's too much.
How is it anyway?
It's the best location.
- That's a strategy too. Raise it.
- Shall I raise it?
(Jung Ho Young, 330 dollars)
He'll do it.
It's 340 dollars.
- We have a 350-dollar bid.
- Will we be okay?
- How about 360 dollars?
- Keep going!
- We have a 360-dollar bid.
- Again?
How about 370 dollars?
(Hoon, 360 dollars)
We have a 370-dollar bid.
How about 380 dollars?
Immediately without hesitation...
That's how it's done.
How about 370 dollars?
Hold on a second.
- Let's think.
- This is...
I knew right then. If I backed down now, I'd lose it.
I tried to look confident with my arms crossed.
We have a 390-dollar bid.
Four hundred...
- Four hundred and ten dollars.
- Goodness.
(Hoon, 400 dollars)
(Will Station A be awarded at this price?)
- Anyone for 410 dollars?
- Even if they win,
they wouldn't make any money.
Four hundred dollars.
Gosh, that's impressive.
Chef Kim Hoon won it with a 400-dollar bid.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Now if we want to win something, we have to bid around 400 dollars.
This could be the lowest price.
It could be the lowest price.
Don't be scared.
I was really happy. With this station,
I'd at least make it to the top three.
The second auction is...
for Station B.
(A place specializing in earthen pot dishes, stews, stir-fried dishes)
(B earthen pot)
As a Korean food station,
it has 2 5-burner cooktops...
and a food warming cabinet.
No other place has a warming cabinet this big.
For rice-based items, it's a really good option.
Right.
You can plate them and send them right out.
I also noticed the refrigerator in the back.
Since these are earthen pots, we can have them ready to go.
(Following Station A,)
(strong competition is expected for Station B.)
The bids will go up by ten dollars at a time.
Ten dollars. Yes.
We have a ten-dollar bid.
Twenty dollars.
Thirty, forty dollars.
- Forty dollars.
- I'll bid one hundred dollars.
One hundred dollars? We have a very confident bid.
I will increase the bid increment...
to 20 dollars.
Anyone for 120 dollars?
- Is your bid 120 dollars?
- I'll bid 200 dollars.
- We have a 200-dollar bid.
- I'll increase it by 100 dollars.
(Choi Sang Hyun, 200 dollars)
What do we do?
I don't like those guys.
Two hundred and twenty dollars?
I bid 250 dollars.
You said that you'd increase it by 100 dollars.
Didn't you say a bid increment of 100 dollars?
- Would you like to bid 270 dollars?
- Yes.
We have a 270-dollar bid.
Two hundred and ninety dollars.
Three hundred dollars.
- Anyone for 320 dollars?
- I'll stop there.
The highest bid is 290 dollars.
Hold on.
Why are you disappearing after raising the price?
I wasn't going to buy it anyway.
We need a shill bidder, don't we?
- A shill bidder.
- Don't we need a shill bidder?
Seung Jae, let's not spend any money.
Seung Jae, we'll keep our spending...
to an absolute minimum.
Pushing the auction price up at the beginning and dropping out...
won't be a bad strategy.
We'll raise the price a little without taking the bid.
(I'll bid 100 dollars.)
(I'll bid 200 dollars.)
Someone else takes it...
and operates at a loss...
while we start from zero.
That could be an advantage for us.
So let's stir things up and get out.
He had no intention of winning the bid,
but he was a villain who kept driving up the price.
We have a 340-dollar bid. How about 360 dollars?
They're not backing down.
Our bid is 360 dollars.
We have a bid. A 400-dollar bid is available.
Now, 400-dollar bids are being called...
like it's nothing.
Shall we keep going?
Just raise it.
We have a 400-dollar bid.
- We actually bought it cheap.
- Anyone for 420 dollars?
- You're good at bidding.
- My goodness.
I'll call out 400 dollars 3 times.
Did anyone make the bid?
- It's 400 dollars.
- He says it's 400 dollars.
Four hundred.
We have...
- a 420-dollar bid.
- All of a sudden?
Four hundred.
(Kim Ho Yoon, 420 dollars)
He's been waiting for 420 dollars.
I'll ask again for a 440-dollar bid.
The highest bid is 420 dollars.
We need to win this fast.
It's 400 dollars.
- But this is too...
- It's very thrilling.
Four hundred and forty dollars.
Jung Ho Young was a little faster.
Kim Ho Yoon, 460 dollars.
Can I get 480 dollars?
If it goes over 500 dollars, we should drop it.
There's no point.
For 500 dollars.
- You're taking your time to decide.
- Five hundred dollars?
- For 500 dollars?
- Five hundred?
- Anyone?
How many plates do you need to sell?
If you'd like to go for 500 dollars...
Jung Ho Young has made a bid.
Can I get 520 dollars?
You can't do this for fun.
- Asking for 520 dollars.
- I'm serious.
- He loves to lift it up.
- I'm so anxious now.
This is driving me crazy.
- Let's stop.
- Five hundred twenty.
- I should've gone for A.
- If there's nobody...
Going once.
- Going twice.
- Bid, people.
Going thrice.
Jung Ho Young, you've won B at 500 dollars.
Congratulations.
You saved 500 dollars.
You got fooled by Ho Yoon!
I got thrown off by him.
I really had the intention to go for it.
You'd pour oil onto it?
Five hundred was our maximum.
It'll become even more heated as it goes on.
It'll become even more heated.
The third one, Station C...
(Next to the Korean food station...)
It's Thai food station.
(It is known for noodle-based Thai food.)
In Station C, you can cook the most variety of food.
Twenty-two dollars.
- He bid 220 dollars.
- I bid 500.
He bid 500. He's leading the bidding once again.
Come on, take it slow.
Five hundred. We got five hundred twenty.
- Anyone?
- Six hundred.
- We have 600.
- Did you say 600?
- Six hundred?
- This is...
- Anyone?
Six hundred is too much.
He's very resolute.
How much is he going to sell?
- Six hundred.
- I'll stop.
If you'll yield...
- Okay.
- If you'll yield...
Going once.
Going twice.
Going thrice.
Chef Kim Ho Yoon won it...
- at 600 dollars. Congratulations.
- How can it get...
- more and more expensive?
- The price rises...
by 100 dollars.
The fourth, Station D.
It's a hot dog food station.
(The kitchen tailored to fast food)
- Anyone for 400?
- I bid 400.
Four hundred.
Chef Lee Sung Hoon won at 400 dollars.
Chef Hong Seok Cheon won at 450 dollars.
Congratulations.
(Kim Hoon: A, Jung Ho Young: B, Kim Ho Yoon: C, Lee Sung Hoon: D)
There are Stations F and G left.
How expensive is F going to be?
Is this all right?
( G: Jeon restaurant, no burner, in a corner)
(F: Chinese food station, Lee Yeon Bok predicted to bid big)
The sixth, Station F.
It's a Chinese food station.
- Chinese...
- I think Chef Lee Yeon Bok...
will win this place no matter what.
This is the only place with a wok.
Station F is the Chinese restaurant.
(Lee Yeon Bok checked out the Chinese restaurant first thing.)
This is better.
There was the burner where we could boil broth.
- There were two Chinese burners.
- Two Chinese burners.
(The only Chinese food station out of the 7 stations)
And all the way at the end.
Where's Station G?
I can't find Station G.
Is that Station G?
I don't know.
Station G is...
G looks a bit lonely.
(Station G, the jeon restaurant, is all the way on the other side.)
Where's the stove?
When I saw a restaurant without a burner...
(There is no burner.)
(It only has a grill...)
(and a cold broth dispenser.)
"It doesn't even have a burner?"
"I can't cook anything here."
This place is tough.
Avoid Station G.
You really can't get Station G.
It won't work.
The competition between Stations F and G will be fierce.
The bid will go over 1,000 dollars.
- What will you go for?
- Stations G or F.
You'll be up against Chef Lee Yeon Bok for F.
I'll raise the bid to 500 and quit. I'll get Station G.
I'll start from zero.
I don't think you can sell over 2,000 dollars.
Chef Lee Yeon Bok will go for...
the Chinese restaurant,
whether it costs 500, 600, or 700.
(A sabotage versus the one who needs it)
The bid will increase by ten dollars.
Ten dollars.
If you lose this, you'll get G.
I bid 300 dollars.
(Choi Sang Hyun: 300 dollars)
- How much?
- I bid 300 dollars.
How much?
- You bid 300 dollars.
- At once?
- Let's go.
- Do you have so much money?
You've bid 310 dollars.
- I bid 400 dollars.
- There he goes.
(Choi Sang Hyun: 400 dollars)
There he goes.
He bid 400 dollars.
Calling for 410 dollars.
- You need to do it.
- Calling for 410 dollars.
The Sauce kept...
increasing the bid.
Increase it to 500 maximum.
- We'll stop at 500.
- Then we can drop it.
Giving up the burner meant...
giving up the competition.
Calling for 410 dollars.
They're taking a long time to think.
Let's go.
If you'll yield,
I'll call for 400 dollars 3 times.
Going once. Going twice.
- Going thrice.
- You should make it 500 dollars.
- Going twice. Going thrice.
- Seriously?
- Nice!
- Chef Choi Sang Hyun...
- won Station F at 400 dollars.
- Nice.
Congratulations.
- You bought it at a low price.
- It's okay.
It's cheap.
I was thinking of taking G for free.
A Chinese cuisine chef didn't take it,
and suddenly...
- Nice.
- I was flustered.
- It's okay. We can do it.
- You're the best.
A professional can work at any kind of kitchen.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
You're cool.
It was a strategy.
When it was announced it'd be an auction...
Since it's a blind evaluation,
it doesn't matter if we're in the corner.
Customers will order from the kiosk anyway.
If it's a blind evaluation, we don't need to bid.
We'll take whatever we have left.
We don't need to spend money...
on bidding for a kitchen.
We'll make use of the promotional banner...
and take good pictures.
Going for G and using the banner is a way too.
It's quite tough without a burner.
Wasn't there a burner in the back kitchen?
There was, but...
That's communal.
The communal kitchen is pretty good.
(Lee Yeon Bok had already checked the communal kitchen.)
The communal kitchen is big.
The last, Station G.
- Ten dollars.
- You bid ten dollars.
- Nice.
- Ten dollars.
- So cool.
- Chef Lee Yeon Bok...
won at ten dollars.
- Congratulations.
- We won.
I was going to win it at ten dollars.
I was going to win it at 10 dollars if the bid went over 500 dollars.
Strategically, it might be a good move.
(Kim Hoon: A, minus 400 dollars, Jung Ho Young: B, minus 50 dollars)
(Kim Ho Yoon: C, minus 600 dollars, Lee Sung Hoon: D, minus 400 dollars)
(Hong Seok Cheon: E, minus 450, Choi Sang Hyun: F, minus 400)
(Lee Yeon Bok: G, minus 10 dollars)
This isn't about sales.
- Including the material cost.
- The material cost.
- It's about operating income.
- Operating income.
In the end, it's about how much you make profit.
That's right.
We must think carefully about...
how many servings to prepare.
Let's drink this.
They got sangria too.
It's very fruity and refreshing.
The orange smells so strong. It's so good.
I don't feel too comfortable.
Surprisingly, it goes well with ham and cheese too.
- Does it?
- Yes.
Will we be okay? I'm so worried.
We need to be really clever with our menu.
(2 weeks later)
(7 hours before the business starts)
(Food court)
(Street Arena)
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy, Eat And Flight)
(Itaewon Class Thai)
(Hororok Samgye Soft Tofu)
Street Restaurant Fighter.
Welcome to Round Four.
(The fourth Street Arena, Incheon International Airport)
I won't go home.
I've come this far. I can't go home.
I agree.
The seven teams opening their stores in the airport food court...
have new signboards, and they can choose the menu...
and the price freely.
From the total sales,
station rental,
(Total sales minus station rental)
promotional cost,
and material cost will be deducted...
to decide the top three teams who will survive.
More than half will be eliminated.
However, until the business ends,
your material costs will not be revealed to each other.
It won't be revealed?
I thought they'd reveal it at the start.
They won't tell us how much in the negative we're starting from.
(The teams' starting sales won't be revealed.)
The material cost could become a variable.
Also, the sales...
will change based on the customer ratings.
- What?
- Customer ratings?
- Based on the customer ratings?
- If your average ratings...
is 5, your sales will be 150 percent of the total sales.
(Average ratings of 5: 150 percent of the total sales)
If you get 4 stars, it will be 125 percent of the total sales.
If you get 3 stars, it will be 100 percent of the total sales.
You're at the baseline when you get three stars.
If you get two stars, it will be...
- This changes a lot of things.
- seventy-five percent.
If you get one star,
only 50 percent of the sales...
- will be reflected.
- The customer ratings are crucial.
That's half gone.
There's a variable.
(The customer ratings weightage has become a lot stronger.)
Now, I'll reveal your new restaurants...
and the amount to be deducted.
Goodness.
(Order kiosk)
Kim Hoon.
Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy.
Chef's meat-packed kimchi stew.
Rental fee, 400 dollars.
Promotional cost, 320 dollars.
The total deduction is 720 dollars.
(Total: Minus 720 dollars)
What? Kimchi stew?
- Kimchi stew?
What?
Eat And Flight.
- Three?
(Premium dried pollack hangover soup set)
What's that?
They have kimchi stew.
They have beef soup too.
- What?
- It's a shame our menus overlap,
but we use black pork.
Total deduction, 500 dollars.
(Jung Ho Young, Eat And Flight, Total: Minus 500 dollars for rent)
- Lee Sung Hoon, Good Morning Earth.
- It looks good.
Koony.
Hong Seok Cheon, Itaewon Class Thai.
Choi Sang Hyun.
Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready...
- in 5 Minutes.
- In 5 minutes.
Total deduction, 650 dollars.
(Choi Sang Hyun, total: Minus 650 dollars)
We must serve our food in five minutes.
Kim Ho Yoon, total deduction.
It's 1,220 dollars.
(Kim Ho Yoon, 1,220 dollars)
(Rent: 600 dollars, promotional cost: 620 dollars)
That's a lot. Is he rich?
I thought they'd place last.
No way can they rank in the top three.
Ho Yoon, will you be okay?
It was fine.
All the top seven contestants are the best of the professionals.
We'll compensate our shortcomings...
by buying the banner slots and providing customers information.
You should take your mom with you.
(Mom couldn't prepare it for you. As a chef, I will!)
The banners are significant.
I was very jealous of Chef Kim Ho Yoon's banners.
Take this to your house.
The last one.
It's just too crowded here.
(Lee Yeon Bok, the Masked Noodle King)
Lee Yeon Bok, rental fee is ten dollars.
- Ten dollars?
- Ten dollars.
(Lee Yeon Bok, rental fee 10 dollars)
That's crazy cheap.
The LED video at the entrance, 250 dollars.
My gosh.
(Lee Yeon Bok, the Masked Noodle King: Minus 250 dollars)
- It's eye-catching.
You can see it as soon as you come up.
(Food court)
The other banners are like,
"What's this piece of paper?"
I only had my eyes on this from the very beginning.
If you guys kept bidding, I'd have bid 1,000 dollars on it.
Ho Yoon.
Bring it here.
What?
- Put the banners there.
- Three banners?
(The banners can be placed anywhere.)
It's Chinese, it looks Chinese,
and there's a video, so it looks very dynamic.
It made you want to eat it.
(Hororok Samgye Soft Tofu, Eat And Flight,)
(Good Morning Earth, Itaewon Class Thai)
Everyone prepared so well.
- Everyone keeps improving, right?
- Exactly.
I don't know.
The business opens...
- from 6am to 9am.
- For 3 hours.
That's crazy.
In this mission, you can get...
one part-timer.
(Each team got their part-timer.)
Now, please start preparing...
for the airport's morning business.
(Time until the business starts)
What I'm worried about is...
for the burners and stuff,
we need to compete... Rather than compete...
We need to share them.
We needed to scramble for equipment.
It was a hectic war.
That was too much.
(The food court has 7 kitchens.)
(All the kitchens connect to...)
(communal kitchens.)
(The communal kitchens, which look like a maze...)
(Kitchen 1)
(Kitchen 2)
(There are only two communal kitchens.)
(From the basic pots...)
(to various pails)
(Even big cauldrons and burners)
(Every team has to share the communal kitchens.)
(Who will secure it first?)
(Kim Hoon is the first to enter the communal kitchen.)
I need to take them.
I need to take them quickly.
What's this? It's too narrow.
(Jong In on his team use the bypath to check out the restaurant.)
Jong In, that fool, where did he go?
Take the equipment quickly.
(He takes everything he can find.)
A few pots... I needed them to boil broths,
but there weren't many.
(The big pails aren't in abundance.)
(Kim Hoon and Kim Jong In quickly take the pails.)
Hey.
Are they using the pots?
(Surprised)
These jerks are already taking them.
(Jung Ho Young and Song Hoon are one step behind.)
That...
I kept it aside for myself.
- This?
- Yes.
(Returning)
(Song Hoon secures the remaining pails.)
This...
We need to secure here first.
(They pour the meat into the communal pot.)
Done.
- Put it here first.
- Okay.
There were two big pots.
One already had meat inside.
- Whose meat is that?
- Ours.
When will you finish using it?
We'll need to use it for a long time.
I just need to boil chicken.
We have no burner inside.
This is the only burner.
I should've thrown some chicken inside first.
The veterans sure are different.
I felt a bit bad,
but we had no choice but to use that burner.
(While they're fighting over the big pot on one side...)
(The other communal kitchen)
(Yu Tae Hui spots a blender.)
(Lee Sung Hoon takes a food pan.)
We were quiet but fast.
We went in fast and left quickly.
I've walked around with no presence many times already,
so I went inside with no presence from the start.
(Lee Sung Hoon quietly took the equipment.)
So I took a lot.
(Thanks to that, they managed to secure enough equipment.)
- That's enough food pans, right?
- Yes, that's enough.
Place small equipment here.
(Team Lee Sung Hoon quietly finishes preparing.)
We were practically ninjas.
(Exclaiming)
I might get lost halfway.
(Team Lee Yeon Bok arrives a lot later than the others.)
We still haven't reached the communal kitchen?
It feels farther than when we checked last time.
Why does it feel so far?
(Unlike other kitchens gathered in the hall...)
The kitchen is one thing, but it's a kitchen in exile.
It's all the way in the corner.
(Yeon Bok's kitchen is in the corner of the food court.)
It's not connected.
(Kitchens A, B, C)
(Kitchens D, E, F)
We need to exit here?
(The way to the communal kitchen is behind the restaurant.)
- Like this.
- Oh, my gosh.
Which way?
We might get lost when we get really busy.
It wasn't even a straight line.
The path was like a maze.
It's this far?
This is bad.
- Here, right?
- Yes.
Look for a pail which can be used to boil broth.
(Team Lee Yeon Bok quickly starts looking for a pail.)
There's a big one.
(But this section's pails...)
Take this.
(were all taken by Team Choi Sang Hyun.)
- This.
- Is this the only one?
- Yes.
- This isn't enough.
- This... Hold on.
- It's too small.
(The other teams have taken all the important equipment.)
- A big pail...
- A pail.
Hold on.
Yes.
Byeong Ho, come here. Can we use this?
(He spots another big pot.)
- Yes.
- They say to use it by agreement.
Let's call dibs on this.
We must take this.
(Team Lee Yeon Bok secures a huge empty pot.)
Even when we didn't use it, we filled it up with water.
I didn't want the others to take it when it became empty.
(It's a battle zone, everyone on alert for a chance.)
It was complete chaos.
It's a war.
There's no pail.
Exactly. We don't have something like this.
(The other teams have secured the pails.)
Look. Those pails...
How did you take them?
Are there more pails?
It's him again.
That team took all the pails.
Give us one pail.
Isn't taking three pails too much?
Sorry?
Will you keep using the pail?
Do you need to keep using it?
If we can use that, I can give you this.
We took this because we didn't have a pail.
We have no burner at all.
If you're done using it, we can exchange.
- If you're done using it...
- We won't be exchanging it.
Because my kitchen has no burner,
we need to move back and forth, all the while boiling broth here.
"You have 3? Then give us 1."
And they asked for the big pot.
We couldn't come to an agreement,
so I said sorry...
and went back to work.
You don't use this, right?
No, not now.
Save it.
Or they'll take it again.
This...
(You must take it first, or it will be taken.)
- Low flame?
- Yes.
Securing a spot is a fight too.
(As the battle for cooking stations rages on,)
(following the battle over equipment...)
Will you be parboiling your abalones?
Yes.
Can I parboil mine with yours?
- What?
- Can I parboil our abalones...
with yours?
Before you dump the water after taking the abalones out.
Well...
- Okay.
- We don't have a pot to do that.
(Successfully parboiled abalones in Yeon Bok's pot)
Abalones are done. All that's left is the chicken.
Where do we boil it?
We'll boil it here.
But the broth.
All that's left is the low stove.
(The stove is already packed.)
(Wandering around Yeon Bok again)
So...
Let's use a tray.
- What is it?
- Let me fill it up...
with new water to parboil the chicken.
That's all you'll do, right?
Yes, I won't boil the soup here.
Okay.
We need to use it right away.
Got it. Parboiling the chicken is all I'll do.
(Succesfully parboiled the chicken in Yeon Bok's pot)
I'll empty the pot and wash it.
Don't throw it away. Leave it.
- Should I leave it?
- Yes.
Let's use it as broth.
Chicken broth?
Yes, as chicken broth.
- I'm sure it's rich.
- Good.
(What's the menu Team Yeon Bok prepared today?)
Fire is everything when it comes to Chinese cuisine.
It's cooked to perfection only under high heat.
There weren't any stoves in the kitchen.
No stove really shocked me.
(A corner kitchen won with 10 dollars)
(Key feature: No stovetop)
Even paying ten dollars for it felt like a waste.
It should've been offered for free.
Or an additional 200 dollars...
should've been offered to the team that uses it.
- Yes.
- That should've been the condition.
Exactly. It was so inadequate that the kitchen...
- felt like a penalty.
- Yes, a penalty.
(A strategic choice, but unfavorable conditions)
This is to cook jeon.
- Right?
- Griddle.
That was the only equipment we could cook hot food.
Wait, this is a slushie.
- A slushie.
- It's not the frozen type, right?
- Like a slush.
- Yes.
(And a cold broth machine)
Like this?
(All they have are a griddle and a cold broth machine.)
Not having any stovetop is...
(Yeon Bok's decision under such condition)
During business...
No fire?
Then let's go with an ice-cold menu.
If you watch those coming to the airport,
some come in rushing,
carry heavy suitcases, and such,
making them all hot and sweaty.
So the menu we chose was...
Chinese-style naengmyeon.
Let's try naengmyeon.
We boldly chose naengmyeon.
(Chinese-style naengmyeon)
(Served in an icy broth with seafood,)
(vegetables, and peanut butter)
On top of the naengmyeon are abalone, jellyfish,
and shrimp.
It's a luxurious and hearty meal.
(Chinese-style abalone naengmyeon)
(Prepping 6 hours before business)
Find a cooking station.
(300 servings worth of shrimp)
(2 boxes of abalone, a total of 310)
(Prepared more than 300 servings of seafood)
Time is literally flying. This is bad.
(Turning on the heat of the only stovetop and big pot)
- Pour both in.
- All together?
Yes, all together.
In the big pot,
we were going to stir-fry, parboil, and boil.
Shucking the abalone takes the whole day.
This is practically a banquet hall.
You're right.
It's like making a 300-serving banquet with 3 people.
Since we sell out really fast,
let's try and sell as many as we can this time.
(During Round 1)
(We'll be out of mianbao xia in no time.)
(Short of mianbao xia)
(During Round 2)
(Oh, no. I'm not sure if we can serve all the orders.)
(We have about 10 servings left.)
(But 10 isn't enough.)
(Sold out early again due to not enough quantity)
Customers really flock to the food court.
Sell 300 servings, and we'll definitely win.
That's what I think.
The shrimp is good.
(Parboiled all seafood)
It's been perfectly parboiled.
- The shrimp is plump.
- Right?
Let's move on to the next step.
(Abalone, squid, carrots, egg garnish)
(Cutting up 300 servings worth of toppings)
(Done setting up the toppings in perfect uniform)
What? It's already past 2am?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
Time goes by so fast. We're doomed.
(The reason Yeon Bok is in a rush is that...)
(today's menu isn't solely Chinese-style naengmyeon.)
Next to the Chinese-style naengmyeon...
are yukjeon, zucchini jeon, and dumplings.
Those three come as a meal.
(Chinese-style naengmyeon with jeon and dumplings, 17.8 dollars)
(Zucchini jeon, yukjeon)
(Handmade dumplings)
I'm known for dumplings.
So today, we came in with a little cheat code.
We'll feel relaxed once we get the dumplings done.
Where are the eggs? 100 eggs.
Let's fry them and then add them to the filling.
It's so far away.
This is practically a marathon.
(Pouring in 100 eggs)
What is that?
- It's for the dumplings.
- Oh, my.
We're making egg chive dumplings. This is the filling.
Is that the filling for the dumplings?
Yes, China has egg chive dumplings.
That sounds delicious.
(Eggs stir-fried over high heat)
(Finely chopped chives)
(Mix them together, and the dumpling filling is ready.)
(Even the dumpling skins are made from scratch.)
From the skin to the filling,
the dumplings are wrapped and handmade right here.
(Hand-shaping them carefully)
Place the wrapped ones here.
Wrap, griddle, and repeat. We'll cook them as we go.
(The handmade dumplings are placed one at a time on the griddle.)
(Time is flying towards the opening hour, 6am.)
It's 4am.
- What?
- It's 4am.
Is it?
(After making dumplings for 2 hours)
Is this the second row?
- Third row.
- Third? How many are there?
Each row has 30, so a total of 90.
Ninety.
From what I see, we should reduce our target servings to 200.
We also have jeon to cook.
(Will they be ready in 2 hours?)
I'll start cooking the kimchi stew fast.
Okay, I'm going to cut the dried pollack.
- The radish can wait.
- Yes.
The customers are going overseas.
Whether they're traveling...
or studying abroad,
they leave for various reasons.
Leaving after having a hot, hearty meal...
seemed like a good idea.
(Eat And Flight)
Eat And Flight.
Why make kimchi stew when they are Japanese and Western cuisine chefs?
Weird.
I specialize in Japanese cuisine.
But my mom ran a Korean restaurant...
for over 40 years.
(On the day of the auction)
What's calling you right away?
- For breakfast.
- Honestly, 1 or 2.
(Out of the 7 food stations)
Stations A or B.
(A and B sell traditional Korean food.)
What about the foreign customers?
The foreign customers...
are leaving Korea.
They want Korean food for their last meal here.
When you go overseas,
the last meal you have is usually one of that country's.
Korean food.
(Korean food that works for all customers)
Korean food is the winning move.
No lose, just win.
The menu I thought of...
Because of these?
One main meal with three side dishes.
This is a rice bowl, right?
The earthen pot is the key to us.
(Using the earthen pot)
When it comes to breakfast,
warm dishes...
like soup and food served in broth are more likely to win...
than cold dishes.
The menu items we prepared are...
Korean beef soup set.
premium dried pollack hangover soup set,
and Jeju black pork kimchi stew set.
Those three.
(3 killer K-earthen pot menus)
I'm shoveling for the first time in years.
(Making kimchi stew in the hard-won pot)
First off, kimchi...
is surely important in kimchi stew.
But it's the pork inside.
To make our menu unique,
we used black pork.
Let's make a menu the customers want to try.
(A simple, everyday dish)
(Emphasizing the Jeju black pork)
(Jeju black pork kimchi stew)
The highlight of the beef soup is the Korean beef.
(The most expensive dish, made with premium Korean beef)
Beef tallow from Korean beef.
The Korean beef is cooked in beef tallow.
(Beef tallow: Rich and savory, used in high-end dishes)
I put in a great deal of time making the red chili oil.
(A flavor-packed Korean beef red chili oil base)
Packed with the rich flavor of Jeju Korean beef,
it's a spicy Korean beef soup.
If the customers want something with a kick,
they can choose between soup and kimchi stew.
If they want something gentle and mild,
they can go for dried pollack hangover soup.
(Royal dried pollack hangover soup)
(3 earthen pots for customers with different tastes)
(Next to Eat And Flight with a Korean cuisine strategy)
Nice.
Are you making the kimchi stew there?
Why not cook it outside?
Chef Song Hoon is using it until 4:30am.
What? So he's not letting us use it.
He promised to cook it fast.
I doubt he'll be done by 4:30am.
Seriously?
Let's cook the rice first.
It was my biggest concern.
Everyone seemed to be going for Korean cuisine,
which means they'd need the stew pot.
But there were only two stew pots.
(Stew pot 1: Lee Yeon Bok of the Masked Noodle King)
(Stew pot 2: Jung Ho Young of Eat And Flight)
All are being used.
As I had predicted, we had no pots to use...
and couldn't use them until the end.
(The other team's kimchi stew was completed in the pot they lost.)
(Impressed)
It's perfect.
I'd love to just dig into that with rice right now.
Try the other team's kimchi stew.
- Shall I?
- Visit and try Hoon's.
Did you cook your kimchi stew?
Not yet.
- I came to taste it.
- I'll call you when it's done.
The kimchi stew is nerve-racking.
- Sorry?
- We're cooking the same menu.
It's making me nervous.
We'd be compared right then and there.
Exactly.
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy, Eat And Flight)
(Chef's meat-packed kimchi stew by Kim Hoon)
(Jeju black pork kimchi stew set by Jung Ho Young)
Chef Jung Ho Young serving kimchi stew...
got on my nerves.
(Kim Hoon versus Jung Ho Young)
(The two's coincidence wasn't a first.)
(Kids Restaurant by Kim Hoon is serving it.)
(Cotton candies!)
(In the previous round interview)
(Complimentary cotton candies)
(Freebie cotton candies)
(Our strategy is to serve...)
(complimentary churros.)
(Children's favorite)
(Churros)
(Their strategy and menu overlapped even in the previous round.)
Our biggest competition is...
(After naming each other the biggest competition,)
(the two teams are against each other again.)
Teams Chef Kim Hoon and Chef Jung Ho Young.
The scariest teams.
There are reasons behind...
every location selection and more.
What's more, the results always follow.
Have you heard that sales go up 1.5-fold...
if the food rating is five?
- The food needs to be good.
- I'm confident in that.
You sure? I'll trust you.
Yes, go ahead.
(Team Kim Hoon starts on the kimchi stew.)
I'll be generous with the perilla oil.
(Next to Team Jung Ho Young's Jeju black pork kimchi stew set)
(Meat-packed kimchi stew by Kim Hoon)
The name of the menu is perilla oil kimchi stew.
The perilla oil aroma is a must.
(Generous amount of perilla oil)
(Generous amount of meat)
The stew is packed with meat.
After pan-frying the meat in perilla oil,
it's fried again with kimchi.
The broth is nice and clear because it's made only with vegetables.
The broth is complete...
after adding rice water.
It needs finishing touches.
Every time the broth is scooped, the perilla oil aroma gets lost.
The later customers won't get to enjoy it.
- Let's drizzle some oil...
- Okay.
when served.
(Kim Hoon's kimchi stew with perilla oil as the kick)
It's already been proven with data.
The food is already being sold at food courts.
Seaweed soup, beef and radish soup,
kimchi stew, and soft tofu...
were in Sections A and B.
I knew those were the best sellers.
(Team Kim Hoon)
(Both teams chose kimchi stew for similar reasons.)
(Team Jung Ho Young)
But Chef Jung Ho Young is making kimchi stew.
That team's chefs have years of business experience.
They already know which menus sell well.
(Overlapped data)
(Who will be the strongest chef in this round?)
We only have 1.5 hours left.
(Until business hours)
Is the spicy stir-fried pork ready to cook right away?
- The spicy stir-fried pork? Yes.
- Yes.
(And Kim Hoon's other strategy)
(Free when you order kimchi stew at A Restaurant)
(Spicy stir-fried pork, fried egg,)
(instant cup noodles, caramel pudding)
Instant cup noodles?
Fried egg.
That's another strategy.
(Sighing)
That's a great idea.
It's the art of business.
(Placed right next to the menu...)
(and in the center of the restaurant are the sales hooks.)
Customers get a lot of freebies if they choose our menu.
First, spicy stir-fried pork.
(Spicy stir-fried pork)
(Fried eggs)
We have enough fresh cream, right?
Yes.
And pudding.
(Homemade dessert, caramel pudding)
When I studied with the bear costume on...
in the previous round,
the team serving many freebies advanced to the next round.
(Complimentary cotton candy!)
(You came for that, right?)
(With data collected from the previous round)
How generous the serving is has to be highlighted.
What's more,
the number one food that you crave at airports,
on flights, and in lounges is instant noodles.
Let's provide instant cup noodles.
Nobody hates freebies.
It's literally free.
I'm sure the customers will choose our menu.
As I thought, he's good.
As expected, his ideas are novel.
Even though it's part of the set,
it makes you feel like you're getting more for free.
If they don't serve Korean food,
we'll win without any bloodshed.
But even if they do serve Korean food,
our menu will be more appealing.
That team might come in first place today as well.
Jong In, let's check what's left.
We need to get ready in 30 minutes.
- Seung Jae.
- Yes?
I'm going to go and decorate the display case.
Got it.
(The upper section of a promotional display case bought at the auction)
Because I won it for 250 dollars,
our team spent...
the third-most amount of money.
We will begin the promotional item auction.
Number four, the upper section of the display case.
We have 220 dollars.
Two hundred and thirty dollars.
Two hundred and forty dollars.
Two hundred and fifty dollars.
- How far are you going to go?
- I'm going to stop.
Once he called 260 dollars, I was going to pull out...
and congratulate him.
Enough.
Chef Choi Sang Hyun won it with a 250-dollar bid.
- Congratulations.
- Good.
We shouldn't have bought it.
The best move would have been to pull out after bidding more.
It's okay, Seung Jae.
Since we won the display case,
we decorated it...
with raw ingredients to show that we cook...
fine ingredients with our hearts.
It was decorated with rice, fresh Korean wild chives,
and meat.
The ingredients used in the food were displayed neatly.
(Choi Sang Hyun filled the display case with ingredients.)
(Korean beef, rice, ginger, Korean wild chives, garlic)
That was one of the things I thought...
was an absolute no-go.
Making an appeal to the customers is a good idea.
But customers know it as a beverage display case.
If there's fresh meat and garlic in there,
customers might think,
"Won't the beverage smell of them?"
Our team will display photos of the actual dishes...
we are serving.
(Food photos on display to entice customers)
(Order a set menu and get thistle rice balls with wild chive sauce!)
(Choi Sang Hyun, Kim Ho Yoon)
Since we won three X-banners...
(Placing all 3 X-banners next to the kiosk)
The X-banners will be set next to the kiosk.
(Welcome. Never had broth this good before?)
(Planning to grab all the customers' attention)
The other restaurants will hardly be noticeable.
You'll get tons of orders right from the start.
The photos really stand out.
- Right?
- Yes.
It's easy to tell what the menu is.
The menu items are in the top seven.
They'll all taste good.
This is a battle of persuasion.
We will stand out for sure this time.
- It's been seasoned, right?
- Yes.
It is currently 5:45am.
Fifteen minutes left.
Fifteen minutes before business hours.
- Fifteen minutes left.
- Fifteen minutes.
Check everything one last time.
Yes, Chef.
It's hard to believe that we stayed up all night, right?
Yes.
(A morning service prepared overnight)
(7 hours into the preparations)
(Morning has come at the airport.)
(A bustling airport from early morning)
(What will the travelers choose?)
It is currently 5:55am.
Five minutes before business hours.
Gosh, time sure flies.
The kitchen is too far away.
I have no idea where I am.
Let's do this!
- Itaewon Class Thai, - Itaewon Class Thai,
- let's go!
- Hohyung...
- Hojae...
- Let's go!
Round Four, Morning at the Airport, begins now.
The windows are now frosted.
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy, Eat And Flight,)
(Good Morning Earth, the Masked Noodle King)
(Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in 5 Minutes)
(Of the 7 restaurants,)
(only 3 will advance to the finals.)
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy, Eat Before You Go,)
(Good Morning Earth, The Masked Noodle King)
(The customers enter one after another.)
(As you come up,)
(you can see today's Street Arena.)
(The first customers enter.)
- They entered.
- Okay.
Customers are going to pour in soon.
(A family of 4)
(Heading straight to the kiosk without looking around)
What do you want to eat?
(The kiosk allows you to see the entire menu at a glance.)
The Masked Noodle King. Itaewon Class Thai.
Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in 5 Minutes.
I want to eat them all.
(What is the first customers' choice?)
Premium...
Ji Min, do you want to eat dried pollack hangover soup?
Dried pollack hangover soup sounds good.
Mom, I like dried pollack hangover soup.
Okay. You can eat dried pollack hangover soup.
(Jung Ho Young's station, premium dried pollack hangover soup set 1)
(Korean beef soup 1)
Look. Number one, dried pollack hangover soup set.
Okay.
(While the family who ordered finds their seats,)
(the soup in the earthen pots boils vigorously.)
Here's one Korean beef soup.
(Piping-hot Korean beef soup...)
(and dried pollock hangover soup in earthen pots are ready.)
(Call)
I pressed call for these two.
(Call numbers appear on the electronic board.)
(Is it mine?)
(Picking up the food)
Please enjoy it.
- As expected, kimchi stew...
- Is the kimchi stew doing well?
Yes.
Oh, no.
What?
(Ho Young's restaurant is busy with orders pouring in.)
It's here.
One kimchi stew.
- Make it quick.
- It's coming out right away.
- What should I do?
- Kimchi stew.
Kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew, two.
Beef, one.
Ho Young.
- The kimchi stew looks good.
- Okay.
Please select a payment method.
One Korean beef soup.
I'll have the Jeju black pork kimchi stew.
- Do you want kimchi stew?
- Yes, I'll get that.
Got it. Okay.
(Glancing)
You're getting quite a lot of orders.
It's coming out right away.
We put all the food in earthen pots in advance...
so we could boil and serve it quickly.
(Earthen pot waiting section)
I have one here.
(Preheating section)
I'll get it done right away.
Right away.
(Boiling section)
- Boil it hot.
- Yes, I boiled it piping hot.
(Since it was preheated, it boils vigorously in 1 minute.)
The boiling kimchi stew is going out right away.
Kimchi stew.
- Please check the side dishes.
- Okay.
(stir-fried fishcake, radish salad, rolled omelet)
Hang on. Green onion.
(Topped and served immediately)
- Right away.
- Kimchi stew.
I called.
Here's your kimchi stew.
Please enjoy it and be happy.
(Orders are continuously pouring in.)
- What is it?
- Kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew is selling a lot.
It's definitely popular.
Korean beef soup.
Please mix it well before you eat. Enjoy it.
It's perfect. Enjoy it.
(Jung Ho Young's Eat And Flight: 91.2 dollars)
Have a nice trip.
Eat And Flight has surpassed 100 dollars in sales.
Good.
Let's win.
Eat And Flight has surpassed 100 dollars in sales.
Good.
- Nice.
What?
It's 100 dollars already?
They've surpassed 100 dollars already?
I'm so jealous.
- It's not bad.
- What did you say?
It's not bad.
- Right?
- Speak English.
Good.
Kimchi stew.
- Because they have kimchi stew?
- Yes.
So, it's all about kimchi stew.
Kimchi stew? But there's one more team with kimchi stew.
What happened to them?
Kimchi stew.
Please enjoy it.
Be happy.
Eat And Flight? You mean, the one next to them?
This is insane.
Thank you.
(Kim Hoon is selling kimchi stew right next to them.)
That restaurant has orders pouring in.
Which one?
We got a call.
- One kimchi stew.
(Kim Hoon's restaurant received their first kimchi stew order.)
We have to get the food out fast. Got it, Hyeon Jong?
Keep checking the flavor too. And the temperature.
- Kimchi stew.
- One kimchi stew.
I'm so nervous.
(Meat-packed perilla oil kimchi stew, Kim Hoon)
This time, we tried to be fast and accurate.
Fast. Speed was our top priority.
Airport customers need to leave quickly.
It's all right.
For the kimchi stew, you just boil a giant pot and scoop it out.
The kimchi stew is simmering,
and the pork is constantly being stir-fried.
So it takes less than a minute for the food to be served.
Those were the menu items designed around that focus.
I'll give you the food right away.
(Two customers just placed an order and barely sat down.)
(Immediate call)
I think this is the place. Chef's Cooking.
(Getting up)
Already?
(Flustered)
Here's one more. Enjoy it.
(Even the customers marvel at the speed.)
I didn't do it.
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy: 51 dollars)
- Here.
- We just got more orders, right?
Yes, there's one more.
- One more.
- Okay.
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy: 51 dollars)
Two... It's three in total.
- Okay.
- Three in total.
We need three more, right? What?
We're getting busy.
Kim Hoon has surpassed 100 dollars in sales.
- I'll put this down.
- Thanks.
(Fried eggs delivered right on cue)
- Instant cup noodles.
(When cup noodles are needed, they appear right from behind.)
Thanks.
Guys, we have good teamwork.
- Good.
- Good. I pressed call.
Thanks.
We were having the best teamwork,
so it felt very reassuring.
Three kimchi stews.
- Three kimchi stews.
We're selling well.
This is nice.
- You ordered kimchi stew, right?
- Yes.
Here's your food. Enjoy it.
Enjoy it.
- Three kimchi stews.
- Okay.
(Kim Hoon is closely gaining on Jung Ho Young.)
I pressed it.
Here.
- This is unbelievable.
- I know.
In perfect order.
Okay. One kimchi stew.
- One kimchi stew.
- I'll press the call right away.
- It's just one order.
- Okay.
(Kim Hoon's restaurant is now calling customers immediately.)
That was incredibly fast.
Kim Hoon has surpassed 200 dollars in sales.
Is it us?
(Nodding)
Good.
We're in first place.
Orders poured in in the beginning,
so I thought selling kimchi stew was the right call.
Only Ho Young's and our restaurants had orders flooding in.
I was happy in the beginning.
(The two restaurants are busy beyond measure.)
(Current Rankings)
(Kim Hoon: 221 dollars, Jung Ho Young: 192.3 dollars)
Both Stations A and B sell kimchi stew.
- Do you want kimchi stew?
- Yes.
Okay. A, one.
(Endless orders...)
(for the undefeated airport menu, kimchi stew)
(Another family of customers is coming up.)
(Arriving in front of the kiosk)
(After pondering for a while)
(The children join in.)
Should we tap them one by one?
Dried pollack hangover soup.
Soft tofu.
This looks delicious.
Premium jjamppong.
- What do you want?
- Jjamppong.
They have rice as well.
I want jjamppong.
Jjamppong?
(Premium jjamppong set)
(Kiosk)
(At that moment, the restaurant located far away)
I thought we would not be ready.
All done.
You said we had about 200 dumplings, right?
- We have 210 dumplings, right?
- We have 210.
Okay.
(They start out with 210 portions prepared.)
We will do it while running the restaurant.
(Order)
One jjamppong set.
One jjamppong set. Hurry.
The jjamppong broth is here,
and the clear broth is here.
Okay.
(If naengmyeon is the standard for refreshing,)
(this is another menu item in charge of the spicy kick.)
(Premium jjamppong set)
It wouldn't be enough to have only cold dishes.
(Infusing the chili seasoning with plenty of smoky flavor)
(Jjamppong seasoning base)
I'll clean it up.
(Putting it into the chicken broth)
(Jjamppong broth is complete after boiling deeply for 1 hour.)
(Shrimp, abalone, squid)
(Utilizing the premium seafood from naengmyeon as is)
(Along with the premium naengmyeon,)
(they launched the premium jjamppong as well.)
(The same combo for 17.8 dollars)
(Refreshing naengmyeon and spicy jjamppong)
(Spotting the electronic display upon entering)
(The menu display of Lee Yeon Bok's the Masked Noodle King)
(Photos of naengmyeon and jjamppong catch your eye from the entrance.)
(Heading to the kiosk after seeing the display)
Where's the Masked Noodle King?
Jjamppong? Do you want the premium jjamppong?
(From the same group)
Order naengmyeon for me.
Is this it? I'll order this.
I'll have naengmyeon.
(1 premium jjamppong, 1 premium naengmyeon)
(Order)
We have 1 more jjamppong set. It's 2 in total.
(Another order)
- Two?
- Yes.
One naengmyeon.
Okay. Two jjamppong and one naengmyeon orders.
(Lee Yeon Bok: 53.4 dollars)
Orders will start flooding in soon.
We have to send out the food within five minutes.
Okay.
- Send out the two servings first.
- Okay.
(Placing the noodles from the noodle cooker)
Jeon.
(Passing it to the topping section.)
Top it with shrimp and abalone.
- Okay.
- And the ones in the bottom...
Hurry.
(Placing the jjamppong toppings over the noodles)
Jjamppong. It's jjamppong again.
Abalone.
Jjamppong broth.
This looks good.
(Pouring in a generous splash of jjamppong broth)
(Meanwhile, Yeon Bok...)
(refries the jeon and dumplings right on time.)
- Call both.
- Okay.
All right. Two jeon sets.
- Did you call them?
- Yes.
(The jjamppong set is ready in only 2 minutes.)
(A jjamppong order)
- It's jjamppong.
- Nice.
Let's go.
(While they are rapidly clearing orders within 2 minutes,)
(a group of foreign customers enters.)
Look at this.
Order received.
Please retrieve your card.
(Instantly selecting the Masked Noodle King)
(Naengmyeon and jjamppong)
(Ordering 1 jjamppong set)
- One jjamppong set order came in.
- One jjamppong.
One jjamppong.
Is this the effect of the display board?
Orders for food from a kitchen that can barely be seen came in.
Things were going well. We were off to a good start.
(The Masked Noodle King: 106.8 dollars)
We got an order. One naengmyeon.
(The Masked Noodle King: 124.6 dollars)
(Back-to-back orders)
Another naengmyeon order.
Okay.
We surpassed 100 dollars too.
(The Masked Noodle King: 142.4 dollars)
- The Masked Noodle King...
- There.
has surpassed 100 dollars in sales.
Are you number 503?
(They clear orders at overwhelming speed.)
Are you number 5,003?
All right. Enjoy it.
(The moment the previous customer picks up their food,)
(they serve the next customer.)
Enjoy it.
(The result of clearing orders without rest)
Currently in third place...
is Lee Yeon Bok.
- We're in third place.
- What a relief.
I'm so relieved. We're in third place.
(The kimchi stew groups are currently in the lead.)
(1st: 359 dollars, 2nd: 312 dollars, 3rd: 231.4 dollars)
(Lee Yeon Bok begins a fierce pursuit in 3rd place.)
(The transit passengers who ordered the jjamppong set)
(Premium jjamppong set)
This is good.
Isn't it nice?
- Yes.
- It's really good.
(Slurping)
I can't believe this is just airport food.
Local Korean food must be amazing.
- Their street food.
- Yes.
Okay. I made up my mind after eating this.
I want to visit Korea again to properly enjoy the food.
How about you?
- Good?
- Great.
- This is really good.
- Do you like it?
(Lee Yeon Bok's jjamppong set, Jung Ho Young's kimchi stew)
- This is really good.
- But...
Good Morning Earth.
(A somewhat chilling good morning)
Our niche market strategy...
- needs to work.
- I know.
(Lee Sung Hoon won the bid for the hot dog station.)
(I bet this is a burger place.)
- Like patties.
- Right.
Let's avoid D. Not D.
I don't want this.
There will not be much we can do in D.
(The kitchen is tailored for fast food,)
(many of them wanted to avoid it.)
(Lee Sung Hoon won the hot dog station.)
(What is he going to make?)
This is actually better.
Even among the existing booths, the hot dog spot...
was the only Western food outlet.
Then we should do Western food here too.
Why don't we just focus...
entirely on foreign customers?
That's a good idea.
Because for foreigners,
- a grilled cheese sandwich...
- Yes.
is an absolute classic. And tomato soup.
That sounds good.
(Grilled sandwich)
(Grilled cheese sandwich)
(Grilled egg and cheese sandwich)
(Grilled ham and cheese sandwich)
We prepared sandwiches...
and set menus that include sandwiches.
(Grilled cheese sandwich set, 22 dollars)
It also includes hummus and salad inside.
We also included a fried egg...
and home fries, which are potatoes stir-fried with onions.
It comes with white ragu we made...
and a duxelles made with mushrooms.
(When the menu was revealed a while ago)
- What is this?
- Sandwich?
The ragu sounds good.
Their mouths were saying it looked good,
but their eyes were saying, "There goes one team."
Everyone's eyes looked so excited.
Like, "We will beat at least one team."
"We have at least one underneath us."
I honestly thought it was not a good idea.
You'd want a proper meal,
not just a sandwich.
Once you enter a food court.
I thought all the chefs here would cook Korean food.
We decided to switch our target entirely...
and focus on foreigners.
And instead of first place, we set our target ranking...
at third place.
We planned to aim for third place by targeting the niche market.
That was our plan.
Please let a lot of foreign customers come.
What if it just ends up staying as a niche?
We wanted to greet people with the feeling of welcoming...
all the mornings in the world.
That is why we came up with the name Good Morning Earth.
We want to approach foreigners in a more familiar way.
(Will the niche strategy targeting foreigners with Western food work?)
(Foreign customers enter right on cue time.)
I'm not sure.
Oh, yes.
(Approaching the kiosk to order)
I hope those foreign customers order ours.
Those two?
They already ordered. They have the receipt in hand,
so they didn't order ours.
They are heading over to the far right.
(Passing right by Seok Cheon's team)
Hello.
(Lee Sung Hoon's restaurant)
(Good Morning Earth: 1 order)
Enjoy.
(Good Morning Earth: 2 orders)
(A family of foreign customers)
I think I'll have the white ragu.
(All members of the foreign family ordered sandwiches.)
(Another foreign customer is ordering right next to them.)
(Picking a sandwich)
(1 order)
Okay. One special set.
White ragu sandwich.
- Grilled ham and cheese sandwich.
- Okay.
- Have a nice trip. Thank you.
- The ragu is ready.
Hello. Your number, please.
(Good Morning Earth: 8 orders)
(Good Morning Earth: 9 orders)
Thank you. Enjoy.
(Out of 14 cumulative orders,)
(10 are from foreign customers.)
- Two ragus, right?
- Yes.
Hello.
Can you give it five minutes?
- Five minutes?
- Yes.
I'll get my bags from downstairs and come back.
Okay. Then, come back...
Sure. Okay.
- Hi.
Could you let me know where the sugar and creamer are?
(It's not easy to deal with foreign customers.)
Are you asking for the hall...
- Server?
Sugar? Yes, and creamer.
(Succeeded in targeting foreign customers)
(Failed in handling foreign customers)
(Business isn't easy today as well.)
(The foreign family who ordered three kinds of sandwiches)
(Special set, white lagu sandwich, grilled ham and cheese sandwich)
You should try this. Give me half of that one.
(Splitting in half and sharing)
It's so good.
(Crunchy)
You like the sandwich, right? It was good.
Yes.
The ragu was delicious.
It tastes like a Philly cheesesteak.
It was a 5 out of 5.
(A special flavor compared to the other dishes eaten together)
- You want a piece of these?
- Sure.
Okay. Here we go.
- Cheers.
(Crispy)
Pretty good. I feel like I've had it before.
Yes. It's good.
- Really good, though.
- Yes.
Five stars. A hundred percent.
Five. I want to bring more than five. Is that possible?
Please retrieve your card.
- There's still time left.
- What are you going to have?
Do you want to try one?
But we won't be able to finish everything.
- How about Good Morning Earth?
- Sure.
(Exclaiming)
(They chose the vegetarian combo.)
Hey. This soup looks good.
It's not bad.
(Trying the tomato soup)
- It's sour.
- Yes.
I like it.
You like everything.
That's not true.
- Do you want to try dipping it?
- Go ahead.
Isn't that what it's for?
(Exclaiming)
It's not bad when you dip it in the soup.
In the US culture,
it's normal to dip the grilled cheese sandwich...
in the tomato soup.
Or they dip the crispy toast in the soup.
(Stir-fry onions, carrots, and celeries.)
(Then mix them with tomatoes.)
Next, grind everything.
Use the fresh cream and butter...
to make it thick.
(Tasty and sour tomato soup is ready.)
It's ready.
Have a nice trip. Thank you.
(30 minutes since business began)
The current sales.
Zero.
Someone has zero sale?
The current sales.
Zero.
Someone has zero sale?
It's depressing to have no orders.
That's devastating.
(While quite a number of customers is having a meal,)
(it's quiet in front of one restaurant.)
The current sales. Zero.
Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in Five Minutes.
(Exclaiming)
What's happening?
I feel bad.
How could we get zero orders?
Maybe the POS system is broken.
I've never received any orders for this long before.
I don't know what to do.
Are you selling any?
- What?
- We haven't sold one yet.
- Not even one?
- No.
- What's your item?
- Beef bone soup.
Why isn't beef bone soup selling?
Not even one?
- How is that possible?
- That's what I mean.
(No single order on beef bone soup)
The first restaurant to survive is...
(1st in Round 1)
(Winning 2 nil in Round 2)
Kids Restaurant survived.
(The strongest restaurant that ranked 1st in Round 3)
Can you believe it?
(They lost confidence.)
Not being able to sell a single order?
(Choi Sang Hyun hits rock bottom.)
How can we get no orders at all?
Please give me power, Ms. In-law.
Give me strength.
(Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in 5 Minutes)
Who's this?
It's someone's face.
- Are you stealing that picture?
- No.
Who's that lady?
She's my in-law.
She's 92 years old.
Grandma's picture builds trust.
Just like that bossam restaurant.
The name is...
Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in Five Minutes.
People don't have much time to eat at the airport.
They're in a rush to leave.
So I thought the beef bone soup with rice was the best.
My in-law makes that soup when she makes kimchi.
I really enjoyed her radish soup.
So we got her radish soup recipe...
and made it simple and tasty.
It's easy on the stomach in the morning.
We don't only serve meat soup,
but also pork bulgogi.
People can have...
soy sauce based bulgogi with white rice.
It's Korean Spring Beef Soup Meal with Bulgogi.
(Korean Spring Beef Soup Meal with Bulgogi for 19 dollars)
(Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in 5 Minutes)
(Choi Sang Hyun's restaurant is filled with the wok noise.)
To make Korean food in a Chinese restaurant,
it was more difficult.
(A former western cuisine chef...)
(making Korean...)
(in a Chinese kitchen?)
I fell for my own trick.
(He raised the bid by 100 dollars.)
(Fine.)
(Take it.)
I was flustered.
Please. Please place an order.
(Current sales: 0)
(Current time: 6:40am)
What should we eat?
(1 order)
Halfway through...
We got an order.
- What?
- Yes.
(The 1st order after 40 minutes)
Congratulations.
Did you get an order?
- Finally.
- Finally, you got it.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
I'll prepare the delicious meat.
(The first order makes them smile.)
(Beef bone soup finally sees the light after four hours.)
Make it delicious, please.
Got it.
People will like our food once they try it.
(Sprinkling Korean wild chives that smell like spring)
- What kind of oil is that?
- It's the perilla leaf oil.
- The perilla leaf oil?
- Yes.
We made oil with perilla leaves.
If you infuse perilla leaves in oil...
instead of adding it directly to the broth,
it leaves a fresh scent...
of perilla leaves.
It's a subtle touch...
from the chef.
We're serving almost in a minute.
We could've done it faster, but we took our time.
- Thank you.
- The beef bone soup has...
the perilla leaf oil.
It makes the soup even more savory and fragrant.
- Really?
- Enjoy.
We...
What's this?
You can have that...
after you finish your meal.
Why do I have to finish my meal?
What do you think?
It's meat.
The meat is swimming.
That's right.
- This is good.
- How does it taste?
It's delicious.
It's delicious. That's how you say it.
- Mom. Look.
- Okay.
Now...
That's what you do.
Let me try.
(Exclaiming together)
(The Korean wild chives beef bone soup has the fresh scent of spring.)
Here's the current customer ratings ranking.
- We just need to get five stars.
- Right.
That will increase our sales by 1.5 times.
- Keep checking on the taste.
- Yes.
First place, five stars.
Choi Sang Hyun.
Maybe they didn't sell much.
How did they get five stars?
That's what I mean.
That's crazy.
But he's always good.
Our customer ratings were good thanks to him.
Was it leaf mustard?
- Never mind. Perilla leaves.
- Can I try it with rice?
Or is it basil?
Is that basil?
It has basil oil or something.
Beef bone soup?
(Trying after hearing the news)
I want water.
This is good.
- It's good.
- Yes.
- My child likes it, so five stars.
- Really?
- Five stars?
- Yes.
- Five?
- Five.
- Is there a reason?
- It's just really good.
- Really good?
- Yes. Really good.
Thank you so much.
(My child really liked it.)
(Good light soup for breakfast)
(My 32-month-old loves it.)
(5 stars from 7 orders)
It's okay...
as long as people like it.
This is really high quality.
If the average customer ratings are five,
that increases our sales by 1.5.
It's not over until it's over.
We just need to maintain five stars.
- We don't know yet.
- We can do it.
- Okay. The other way.
- The other way.
(Choi Sang Hyun's team plans to turn it around...)
(with overwhelming customer ratings.)
(Customer ratings ranking after 1 hour)
(1st: Choi Sang Hyun, 5, 2nd: Kim Ho Yoon, 4.5)
(3rd: Lee Yeon Bok, 4.33, 4th: Jung Ho Young, 4.3)
Itaewon Class
Beautiful rice.
Whoosh.
(Practicing serving)
(Hong Seok Cheon and Park Min Hyuk are waiting for orders.)
(Order)
One Breakfast Pho Combo.
Let's go.
I wanted to try Thai food in one of the rounds...
because it means a lot to me.
(Hong Seok Cheon prepared his ultimate Thai food.)
(Thai Breakfast Pho Combo for 17.9 dollars)
(Corn som tam salad, pork rice bowl, chicken pho, crabmeat omelet)
I brought my favorite Thai chef in...
as a special guest.
(Chef Paw is currently running a Thai restaurant.)
He's also an expert in cooking.
That's right.
The chef used...
his own recipe.
He used the chicken stock for the sauce.
Sugar, oyster sauce, and the fish sauce.
(Finishing up with the Korean sour flavor)
Nice.
(The soup made spicy with the Thai chili seeds)
(Add a basket of drumsticks.)
(The base soup is ready.)
Chef Paw, how long does it take? One minute?
- Yes.
- All right.
(Boil rice noodles and mung bean sprouts for a minute.)
(Add the chicken and broth to the noodles, and it's ready.)
(Chicken pho)
(Trying the soup first)
(Exclaiming)
Is it good?
I should've had a drink last night.
- I have.
- Try this.
- Excuse me.
- Help yourself.
(Asking for a sip of pho)
(Exclaiming)
That's really good.
- That's the best pho ever.
- Really?
It's the best soup I've ever had.
Right?
I've never had anything...
- like this before.
- I know. It's so good.
I need to take it home.
- I want to keep it in my tumbler.
- Me too.
(Current time)
Surpassed 1,500 dollars in sales.
Currently in first place...
(Stunned)
Already?
(Gasping)
Where? Who made 1,500 dollars?
(Among the 7 restaurants,)
(who made 1,500 dollars in sales?)
- Thank you.
- Yes.
(Kim Hoon and Kim Jong In?)
Four Korean beef soup and two kimchi stews.
Two kimchi stews are coming up.
Two orders of jjamppong are done. So only one naengmyeon left?
- Yes.
- Here you go.
(Lee Sung Hoon and Yu Tae Hui)
Have a nice trip.
(Which restaurant made 1,500 dollars first?)
(Eat And Flight)
Jung Ho Young.
(Jung Ho Young and Song Hoon made 1,500 dollars.)
Nice.
(Grunting)
- Congratulations.
- The gap with Kim Hoon...
- in second place is 800 dollars.
- No way.
(Currently in 2nd place, Kim Hoon, 704 dollars)
(An hour and a half ago)
Jung Ho Young and Kim Hoon...
have surpassed 300 dollars in sales.
They're competing closely with only a 20-dollar gap.
Good job.
Two kimchi stew. One Korean beef soup and one kimchi stew.
- Coming up.
- Okay.
Bravo.
(Jung Ho Young increased the gap by 2 times.)
That's awesome.
Shoot.
(They both sell the kimchi stew.)
(However, it's Jung Ho Young's landside victory.)
Is the earthen pot kimchi stew...
- better?
- What?
Is the kimchi stew in earthen pot better?
The earthen pot is likely to win.
We can't beat the earthen pot.
That looks traditional even to foreigners.
(The restaurants have similar tableware.)
(The Masked Noodle King)
(Itaewon Class Thai)
(Jung Ho Young's earthen pot stands out.)
(Watching carefully)
I don't know what it is, but it's very hot.
What I like about this dish is...
that it's hot, but it's not like...
it's served straight from the boiling pot.
(The effect of earthen pot)
The earthen pot itself has the traditional vibe.
(The earthen pot caught the foreigners' attention.)
Three premium dried pollack hangover soup sets.
Perfect.
Three premium dried pollack hangover soup sets?
Kimchi stew.
I guess we should've made many similar menu items.
That looks professional.
(Jung Ho Young's menu)
(Only consisting of soup with rice)
(3 different types)
That's a soup restaurant.
Let's order from there.
Eat And Flight has the dried pollack hangover soup.
That sounds good.
I'll have the dried pollack hangover soup.
Korean beef soup set, dried pollack hangover soup...
Soup, kimchi stew, hangover soup.
- Dried pollack hangover soup.
- They have everything.
You can order first.
Mom, Eat And Flight has...
The dried pollack hangover soup sounds good.
I'll have Korean beef soup.
What do you want to eat?
(Perfect menu for a group to order together)
- Korean food is the best.
- Korean food is the best. Yes.
(All Jung Ho Young's menu)
(Korean beef soup, dried pollack hangover soup)
(Kimchi stew)
(All Jung Ho Young's menu)
Oh, it's rich.
- It's good.
- Do you like it?
Let's come up with three different types of soup with rice,
so the whole group can order here.
Four kimchi stew. That's seven in total.
One dried pollack hangover soup.
- Kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew?
Set? I like it.
- Perfect.
- It's perfect.
- Bulgogi.
- Jung Ho Young is...
guaranteed to survive with the highest sales.
(By placing the clear number one,)
(Jung Ho Young and Song Hoon are guaranteed to survive.)
- It's ready.
- Serve it...
when it's still hot.
I'm getting anxious.
Number one...
It made me think I'd better do my best.
We only have an hour left, right?
They're way out in front.
Now it's a fight for 2nd and 3rd.
Who will take 2nd and who will take 3rd.
(Only 2 tickets remain for the final.)
This is crazy.
It's not over yet.
Only the best remain.
(Groaning)
Only an hour left.
We never know. We still have an hour left.
(Among the 6 remaining teams,)
(who will be the 2 to enter the final?)
(An hour remains...)
(with 2 tickets to the final)
(They must win over customers in the remaining hour.)
Except for Chef Jung Ho Young, the gap wasn't so big.
Then we can turn it around.
(Now, the customers will...)
(get to see the customer ratings.)
The battle of customer ratings begins.
(The customer's rating...)
(changes their ranking.)
My goal is to maintain five stars.
It's not over until it's over.
(Chased...)
(versus chasing)
(Fight it to the end for the final.)
Morning at the Airport.
Here is the result.
We never know. It was so neck and neck.
(How will the unpredictable semifinal turn out?)
(Now...)
You only have one round left.
(The final)
(Final mission: The restaurant for all)
(A 115.7m² restaurant is built for the final.)
(Starting with the interior design...)
(to customer service and serving)
(They must compete in a real restaurant.)
Goodbye.
(The number of tables)
(Labor cost)
(Ingredient cost)
(Only one team with the highest sales...)
(will survive.)
(Street Restaurant Fighter Winner)
(What's going to happen in the final round?)